



**OGDEN, UTAH** 



+1 469-996-3138



Katherineabela@gmail.com



**@KATABELA** 

## **ABOUT ME**

After completing my studies in Australia I moved to the United States to further pursue my cheerleading career and living out my dreams of moving overseas.

I was a key member of the Weber State University Cheerleading Squad for 4 years, earning 4 consecutive national titles with the team. In addition, also representing Australia several times at international competitions all over the world

My years in cheerleading allowed me to build a significant social media following that has given me valuable insights into creating content that connects with people.

My experience in social media has tied in well with my work experience and degrees in design, web and UX and have allowed me to develop a folio of a wide range of visually compelling content that wholly represents individual brands and organisations.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGN INTERNSHIP**

WEBER STATE UNIVERSITY - EAST CENTER FOR TECHNOLOGY OUTREACH (2023 - 2024)

- Continued to apply design skills while learning and growing within a dynamic team.
- Strong eye for detailed design with brand identity and marketing goals.
- Comfortable learning quickly, communicating with the team, contributing creative ideas, and collaborating on projects.

### SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

WEBER STATE UNIVERSITY COMPUTER LABS (2022 - 2023)

- Strategized to increase lab population, social media followers, and brand awareness.
- Created video content that appealed to a student audience.
- Reviewed social media analytics and communicated with managers to deliver desired content.

## **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**STUDENT ORGANISATIONS

(2021 - 2022)

- Created and designed print, screen-print, and digital materials for Instagram, Facebook, and TV advertisements.
- Responded to design briefs from client organizations across the university.
- Created posters, banners, social media posts, reels, and video/animation content.

### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**OUTLAWS ALLSTARS

(2016-2017)

- Created content for posters, banners, and social media platforms such as their website, Facebook, and Instagram.
- Worked in collaboration with clients to develop content that wholly represented their brand.

# FRONT END SUPERVISOR & CASHIER WOOLWORTHS ASHWOOD

(2010 - 2020)

- Managed the front-end team independently and maintained
- high customer service at all times.
- Able to work quickly and efficiently under pressure.
- Extremely comfortable talking to and dealing with different
- demographics professionally.
  - Comfortable multitasking, organizing, and delegating tasks.



## **EDUCATION**

### WEBER STATE UNIVERSITY

2024 Associates Degree in UX and Web Design

**2022** Certificate in UX Design

**2021** Certificate in Web Proficiency

2016 - UNIVERSITY OF MONASH

2019 Bachelor of Communication Design

2012 PRESBYTERIAN LADIES' COLLEGE

High school VCE diploma

## **TECHNICAL**

### **ADOBE SOFTWARE SUITE:**

Illustrator

Photoshop

After Effects

Premiere Pro

Lightroom

Indesign

### USER INTERFACE DESIGN

LANGUAGES:

HTML CSS

Javascript (React)

## **REFEREES**

#### **SUMMER WILLIS**

Weber State University Head Spirit Director 801 698 7611 swillis@weber.edu

#### **KENNY LA**

Weber State University HR Manager 385 278 3478